Guide to the Frederick Vincent Papers, 1776-1872 RL.01333
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Frederick Vincent papers
1776-1872
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Vincent, Frederick
RL.01333
1 Linear Feet
458 Items
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
Collection was acquired from Mr. Alvin Lohr on November 19, 1956.
Biographical Note
Vincent lived in Norfolk, VA but spent a great deal of time in Washington, DC. He specialized in land and boundary disputes and had several important Washington correspondents.
Collection Overview
Collection contains letters, some from prominent figures in Washington and some addressed to Chilton; court briefs from Norfolk, and several copies of Virginia Land Office records from the 18th century.
Vincent, Frederick
- Accession (56-176)
  - Correspondence, various dates (Box 1)
  - Letters, 1834-1855 (Box 1)
  - Letters, 1855-1858 (Box 1)
  - Letters,1859 (Box 1)
  - Letters, undated (Box 1)
  - Legal Papers, 1776-1872 (Box 1)
  - Legal Papers, undated (Box 1)
  - Bills and Receipts, 1850-1859 (Box 2)
  - Bills and Receipts, undated (Box 2)
  - Printed Matters, various dates (Box 2)
  - Bills and Receipts, 1819-1839 (Box 2)
  - Bills and Receipts, 1840-1849 (Box 2)